lazyfeed.com 2011-02-20

# Lazyfeed

Lazyfeed values and respect the privacy of its users and believes that strong privacy policies are needed across the Internet, so we are providing you with our privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). 

###  Your Information and Our Use 

Lazyfeed offers technology that is provide on a service basis, allowing you to view content (such as news feeds). In order to use the technology, you will need to set up an account, so we will gather the information needed for the account and also some information when you visit our site. In order to provide you with our technology, we may collect the following types of information: 

**Lazyfeed Account:** When you create a Lazyfeed account, your user name, password and email account will be retained in order to allow you to use your account. 

**Website Visit Information:** If you visit our site, we may create a log of your visit with information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type and language, and date and time of your visit. 

**Cookies:** When you visit our site, we may send cookies (little files for your browser that identify your browser and visit). Our policy is to only use cookies to improve our product and services. 

**Communications:** If you send us emails, faxes, letters or other communications we may keep those in order to address your issue and improve our services and products. 

**Personal Information:** For registration for our services and products, we may collect personally identifiable information (like name, address, and email address) (“Personally Identifiable Information”). It is our policy to only use Personally Identifiable Information to provide our product and services, and not provide such to anyone outside of Lazyfeed without your consent. 

###  Questions; Complaints 

If you have any questions or complaints concerning this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at: 

Privacy Policy  
c/o Lazyfeed, Inc.  
1 Hallidie Plaza Suite #304  
San Francisco, CA 94102  
USA 

If we receive any formal, written complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, we will seek to contact you and address your concerns. 

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Although we may revise this Privacy Policy from time-to-time, we will not reduce your privacy rights without your consent. Please note the modification date of the Privacy Policy, as changes are likely to be minor. 

Last modified: August 25, 2009
